here's four proofs that the area of the
regular do deagon in a unit circle is
three the higher the level the better
the
[Music]
proof
yeah yeah sing in the street the sun is
in the East
yeah yeah calling out the Beast the
tiger underneath
yeah yeah I'm starting to believe the
world is at my feet
yeah I'm ready for the feast it's all
within my reach it's all within my
reach I'm going all the way I'm going
yeah my blood is Rebel I'm going all the
way I'm going to another level
[Applause]
if I'm on the loose running after you
yeah yeah there's nothing you can do
I'll catch you when it's through
yeah yeah hle for the juice yeah 120
poof yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm blowing up
the roof blowing up the roof got nothing
left to
Pro I'm going all the way I'm going yeah
my blood is reel going all the way I'm
going to another
[Applause]
level let
go
got to get my hands
dirty chain breaker Earth Shaker rain
maker yeah another level chain breaker
Earth Shaker rain
Earth Shaker rain maker oh to another
level I'm going all the way I'm going
yeah my blood is re I'm going all the
way I'm going to another
[Applause]
level another
Lev let's go let's go let's
go to another
level
you let's get
it let me know in the comments which of
the four is your favorite thanks for
watching